AKASH M S

+1(437) 557-0225



akashkannan71@gmail.com



Scarborough, ON



SUMMARY

Experienced Crew Member with 2 years of dedicated service, known for delivering outstanding customer assistance, food handling and upholding store cleanliness. Skilled in managing inventory, food portioning, and handling cashier responsibilities. Proven adaptability in fast-paced settings with a strong commitment to ensuring customers have a positive and well-organized shopping experience.

EDUCATION

MKM HSS Piravom

High School Diploma - Computer Science 2020-2022

Centennial College, Scarborough Canada

Software Enginnering Technology -A I (ongoing)

SKILLS

Student

- **■** Food Handling and Beverage Handling
- Strong Communication Skills
- Recipe Knowledge and Open Close Procedures
- Inventory Management and Store Cleanliness
- Team Worker and Problem Solving.
- Time Management and Baggage Efficiency

AVAILABILITY

Monday 06:00AM-12:00PM Tuesday 06:00AM-02:00PM

Wednesday 06:00AM-04:00PM

Thursday Full Time
Friday Full Time
Saturday Full Time
Sunday Full Time

Open to work on night shift Everyday!

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Crew Member

McDonalds Kochi | Sept 2022 - Dec 2022

- Operating cash register, food preparation, maintaining hygiene, stocking items and drive-thru customer communication
- Rapidly acquired expertise in POS systems, daily operational protocols, and company guidelines.
- Diffusing situations by listening to customer complaints and offering solutions to enhance customer relations
- Confirming food quality standards and presentation and ensuring the correct temperature for storage
- Performing multiple daily responsibilities, including handling monetary transactions and participating in food preparation

Store Associate

Lulu Hypermarket Kochi | Jan 2023 - July 2023

- Greeted customers upon their entry into the store and helped them with any questions and concerns.
- Managed the cash register and POS software, as well as checkoutlane belt, UPC scanner, and weight scale.
- Performed all checkout procedures quickly and accurately each time, while also promoting the store credit card to customers.
- Processed credit card, debit card, cash, gift card, and store credit transactions

Crew Member

Gelato Shack Pickering | Aug 2023 - Oct 2023

- Prepared gelato shakes and other frozen desserts according to shop recipes and standards.
- Made 12+ varieties of Burgers, sandwiches and wraps everyday without committing single mistake.
- Worked in a fast paced environment as team player and efficiently communicated with the co-workers.
- Regularly cleaned every equipment used for food preparations and ensured food safety and hygiene.
- Experience in the closing procedures like cleaning, safety measures and inventory management.